# TING FURYAN

# PRODUCT MANAGER & TECHNICAL BUSINESS ANALYST

Website: https://ting.furyan.co - Email: ting@furyan.co - Phone: 512-777-1183 - Leander, TX

#### **PROFILE SUMMARY**

Accomplished business analyst able to achieve multiple goals given a solid grounding in technological possibilities and 7+ years in data analysis. History of delivering highly functional software product prototypes for identify and mitigating challenges and risks to bring products to market. Quick to immerse in various projects to become subject matter expert and problem-solve for actionable decisive tasks to achieve results.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Languages: R, SQL, HTML, XML, JavaScript, C++, Salesforce APEX, and BASH

Software: RStudio, REST APIs, Salesforce, JIRA, MySQL Workbench, SQL Developer, Github

Other: Regex, Lean Methodology, Agile, MySQL, Oracle 10.1

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## **Electric Ember, LLC**

## **Co-Founder and Business Manager**

Apr 2013 - Present

- Responsible for all payroll, invoicing, budgeting, bookkeeping, and minor accounting duties
- Expanded e-liquid line into over 10 stores in Central Texas and into several stores out of state
- Main graphic designer and brand manager of product and on pace to grow revenue \$70k year over year

## Morningstar, Inc.

## Senior Business Analyst / Product Manager

Jan 2014 to Present

- Developed the derived data strategy, roadmap, prioritization, value proposition, and business case leading to the signing of clients that were previously uninterested in our other product offerings
- Translated the product roadmap into features and specifications refined and tested with customers (UAT)
- · Lead effort to gather and document functional requirements from clients to detailed written specifications
- Communicated updates on project status, work completed and in progress, next steps, risks, and KPIs
- Increased data offerings from conceptualization, definition, implementation and release for 40+ feeds

## **Vendor Business Analyst**

Sept 2011 to Jan 2014

- Procured new (~10/year) and maintained existing vendor relationships with 200+ global data providers
- Provided ad-hoc and monthly reporting and auditing of client subscriptions per SLA with our data vendors
- Served as escalation point for difficult or unresponsive data partners to resolve client requests
- · Marketed new data offerings and vendor partnerships to raise clients' perception of our value add
- · Managed and delegated challenging, but skill level appropriate tasks to multiple direct report interns

### Senior Data Analyst

Apr 2010 to Sept 2011

- Created guide materials and hosted monthly trainings with for local and remote international operation offices
- Actively sought out new applications and methods to improve the suite of tools available for teams' efficiency
- · Extracted and transformed detailed error log information into concise actionable steps for QA team

# **Data Analyst**

Apr 2008 to April 2010

- Logged and monitored defects or bugs among several hundred reports aggregated in data warehouse
- Performed root cause analysis of data issues and implemented process to prevent repeated events
- Converted raw data into clean and conformable formats for database processing

# **Client Support**

Nov 2006 to Apr 2008

- · Resolved tickets from clients and colleagues in a fast and professional manner for all supported products
- Continually and proactively kept clients updated on the progress of resolving their support request
- Arranged Webex sessions across various departmental teams with clients to expedite resolutions

#### **EDUCATION**